Chicago has failed startups. For years, our founders have
been building and isolation with no communities to support
them. That changes today. Today we're launching Density, an
invite only founder LED collective of Chicago's top
startups. For the past year, we've been working on our
startups together in person, sharing advice and investing
in each other's growth. Our members include YC alums,
Sequoia back founders, exited founders and startups doing
millions in revenue. And now for the first time ever.
We're opening up our applications to the public. We're
looking for the best and brightest entrepreneurs in Chicago
to join us so together we can build successful businesses,
invest as local angels, and repeat the cycle. You don't
have to move to Silicon Valley to build successful startups.
If you want to come work with Chicago's top founders every
single day, apply a Density dot Ventures.
We're here building even on Saturdays, so come join us.